crock-pot.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy at Crock-Pot.com.

**Effective Date: 23 January, 2014**

Information Gathered by Us   
Our Use and Disclosure of Information   
Surveys and Contests   
Third Party Websites   
Updating or Removing User Information   
Opt-Out   
Offline v. Online Practices   
Changes to This Privacy Policy   
Security   
Use by Minors Prohibited   
Consent to Transfer   
Contacting Us

**Effective Date: 23 January, 2014**

Crock-Pot.com is an electronic marketplace for products distributed by Jarden Consumer Solutions (referred to as "we," "us" or "our") and its affiliates. We understand that your privacy is important to you and we established this Privacy Policy to explain what information is collected on Crock-Pot.com (the "Site") and how it is used. By using this Site, you agree to the collection and use of information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this Site. 

**Information Gathered by Us**   
For visitors and registered users to the Site, we log standard technical information, such as your IP address and the kind of browser you are using. If you choose to register with us or make a purchase, you may be asked to provide personally-identifiable information, including, without limitation, name, address, email address, phone number, date of birth and financial account information, such as credit or debit card number ("PII"). We may also collect other PII when you provide feedback or comments online, such as information about our products you own. 

This Site uses first and third-party cookies and tracking technology analytical features for advertising, marketing, click impression reporting, demographic and interest reporting, and similar marketing analytics reporting features. Some of these features are provided by third-parties that support our Site services. Some of these features may allow our third-party providers to track your interests across other areas of the web to inform you of matters related to your interests and to help us optimize our business models. 

We use and allow third parties to use cookies and other web monitoring technologies. For example, we use web beacons to collect information about you and to provide a more tailored and user-friendly service to you. We may use cookies to record session information, such as items that you add to your shopping cart, to record past activity or to provide better service when you return. Authorized third parties may link your name, address and email address to other information which they collect, such as past online/offline purchase information and Web usage from other sites. You can set your browser to refuse cookies, but without our cookies you will not be able to complete a purchase or take advantage of certain features of this Site. 

Pixel tags are tiny graphic files that are included in HTML-encoded email messages. We use pixel tags to gather information about emails sent to our users. When such a message is opened in an HTML-capable email program, the recipient's computer accesses our server to retrieve the pixel tag file, and allows us to record and store the date and time, the recipient's email address, and other standard logging information. These pixel tags may also read cookies. 

**Our Use and Disclosure of Information**   
The information we collect about you in the course of our relationship is used to operate our Site and offer products and services to you. For example, we may use your PII to fulfill your order, to send you information about our company and services, or to contact you when necessary. We may also use your PII to send you periodic emails about new products and services or upcoming events ("promotional email"). In addition, we look at technical information to analyze traffic to this Site, to enhance our offerings and to provide our services to you. For example, we may use traffic information to see which portions of this Site are more frequently accessed and to gather broad demographic information. In connection with these services, we collect non-personally identifiable information, but we will not merge personally-identifiable information with non-personally identifiable information unless you consent to that merger. 

We work with and may share information with third parties who provide services that may include, but are not necessarily limited to, website hosting, data processing and analysis, back-up and security services, and processing of credit card transactions. We may share PII with these service providers for the purpose of providing these services. Although we seek to require these service providers to protect such PII, and to use it only for the purpose for which it was provided, we cannot be responsible for third parties' use of PII. 

In order to provide you with a full range of products and services, we may share your PII with our affiliates for marketing or other purposes. An affiliate means any company that controls, is controlled by or is under common control with us. In addition, we have built relationships with selected partners that are not affiliates, but which offer products or services that may be of interest to our users. If you opt-in to receive information from us we may also share your PII with our unaffiliated third-party partners for marketing or other business purposes. Please refer to the section of this Policy titled "Opt Out," below, if you would like to opt out of having your PII shared with affiliated or unaffiliated third parties for third-party direct marketing. 

We reserve our right to share PII about our users with other third parties, including: (1) with your consent or as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy; (2) when we have a good faith belief it is necessary pursuant to a subpoena or other judicial or administrative order; (3) where required by law; or (4) at our sole discretion, where we deem it necessary to respond to claims, to protect the safety of any individual or the public, or to protect our rights or property or the rights or property of any third party. In addition, we may share aggregated demographic and statistical information with third parties. 

In the event of a change of ownership or corporate restructuring ( _i.e_., a sale, merger, acquisition or transfer of our assets), we may share or transfer your PII to a third party. 

**Surveys and Contests**   
At various times we may offer surveys or contests to users. Surveys may ask for contact information or unique identifying information to increase the value of the results. Contests may require contact information or other demographic or personally identifiable information in order to determine eligibility. We use information collected from surveys and contests to improve our service and to notify and contact winners of various contests. From time to time, a contest may ask users to provide content, such as recipes or tips that make the most of their product, which may be provided to the public. 

**Third Party Websites**   
We do not control the information collection and distribution policies on Internet domains other than this Site. When you are on this Site, you may be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. For example, if you "click" on a link on this Site, the "click" may take you off of this Site. These other sites may independently collect data, solicit personal information, or send their own cookies to you. We are not responsible for any use of the information including click-stream data that you may create when using such third party sites. 

**Updating or Removing User Information**   
You may choose to correct or update the PII you have submitted to us online through the "My Account" page. You may also remove your PII from your "My Account" page by contacting customer service. If you request to have your PII removed from your "My Account" page, we will remove it from its active database, though it may remain stored indefinitely in our back-up media and archival records. 

**Opt-Out**   
We do not disclose an individual customer's PII to third parties for third-party direct marketing purposes if that individual has submitted a request not to have his or her PII shared for this purpose. If you would like to opt out of having your PII shared with third parties for third-party direct marketing purposes, by U.S. mail at: Attention: Direct Marketing, 2381 Executive Center Drive, Boca Raton, FL 33431. Third-party providers, such as Google or Adobe analytics, or similar providers have developed "opt-out" mechanisms that may have unique settings based on your specific browser. Some of these mechanisms are in the form of browser "add-ons" or may be presented in "dashboard" form. Please follow this link to find out more about such features:[ https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)

California residents have the right to request information from us regarding the manner that we may share personal information with affiliated companies and third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To find out what and how we share such information, you may [send us an e-mail request](http://www.crock-pot.com/contactus?cid=contact-us). We will provide: 

A. The categories of information we disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year, if any; 

B. The names and addresses of the third parties who received information for their direct marketing purposes; and 

C. Examples of the products and services subject to the third parties' direct marketing programs, if the nature of the third parties' business cannot be determined from their names. 

In addition, we also allow you to decide whether you want to receive promotional emails from us. You can change or update your email status within the communication that is sent to you. 

**Offline v. Online Practices**   
This Policy applies solely to our collection, use and disclosure of PII obtained online through this Site, and does not apply to any of our practices conducted offline. 

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**   
This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. If we make any substantive changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify users by posting the updated Privacy Policy on this Site. Please periodically review this page to ensure your familiarity with the current version of this Privacy Policy. Your use of this Site after the changes have been adopted constitutes your agreement with the revised Privacy Policy specifically with regard to PII collected from you in the past and in the future. 

**Security**   
We have implemented security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the PII under our control. Although we make good faith efforts to store PII collected by this Site in a secure operating environment, we cannot guarantee complete security. PII held by us will be maintained for a length of time appropriate to our business needs. 

**Use by Minors Prohibited**   
This Site is designed for users over the age of 18. We comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and will not knowingly collect PII from anyone under the age of 13. 

**Consent to Transfer.**   
For those Site users located outside of the United States, we advise you that your personal information may, at times, be accessible by individuals who are located worldwide including in countries that do not provide the same level of data protection as in your country. By providing us with your personal information, you consent to our use of it in accordance with this Privacy Policy, including the transfer of your personal information across international boundaries. We will continue to adhere to the principles stated in this privacy policy and those set forth in applicable laws in connection with any personal information. We will endeavor to preserve the integrity, confidentiality, and security of personal information and afford such personal information an adequate level of protection. 

**Contacting Us**   
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, our practices, or your experience with Crock-Pot.com, please contact us at the postal address. 

**Postal Address:**

Attention: Direct Marketing   
2381 Executive Center Drive   
Boca Raton, FL 33431
